Art of Eight Limbs is a action, thriller film directed by Robert Grasmere.
Four canisters of deadly VX nerve gas have fallen into the
hands of an international arms dealer in Myanmar.
A CIA recruit delivers a high-tech detection device
to an agent already on the ground.
Scott Schiff, played by Ludi Lin.
Mae, played by Grace Vorananth.
General Thiha, played by Sahajak Boonthanakit.
Nick Buckley, played by Nicholas Hammond.
Cho, played by Vithaya Pansringarm.
Gerard, played by Ron Smoorenburg.
The Crow is a 2024 gothic supernatural superhero film serving as a reboot and the fifth installment overall in The Crow film
series, and is the second film, after the 1994 film, to adapt the 1989 comic book series by James O'Barr.
It was directed by Rupert Sanders from a screenplay
by Zach Baylin and William Schneider.
A co-production between France, the United States and the United Kingdom, the film stars Bill Skarsgård as Eric Draven /
The Crow, a man who is resurrected to avenge the deaths of himself and his girlfriend, played by FKA Twigs.
The film entered development in December 2008, with Stephen Norrington stating
that he would write and direct a "reinvention" of The Crow.
It entered a complicated production process with various directors,
screenwriters, and cast members attached at various points.
Filmmakers Norrington, Juan Carlos Fresnadillo, F.
Javier Gutiérrez, and Corin Hardy were initially signed to direct while Bradley Cooper, Luke Evans,
Jack Huston, and Jason Momoa were all cast as Eric during various points in development.
Skarsgård was announced as Eric in April 2022, along with Sanders as director.
Filming began in July, occurring in Prague and Penzing near Munich.
The Crow had its world premiere in New York City on August 20, 2024, and was released in France on August 21 by Metropolitan Filmexport,
and in the United States and United Kingdom on August 23 by Lionsgate and Entertainment Film Distributors respectively.
It received negative reviews from critics and was a box-office bomb, grossing
$24.1 million worldwide against a production budget of $50 million.
The film explores themes of martial arts, undercover agent, action thriller.
The tone is intense.